<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>welcome on candaceblog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1314/</link>
    <description>Recent content in welcome on candaceblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1314/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>first post: testing the ping vibes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>this is a test post to demonstrate the clean app-style interface inspired by the candaceserver ping service.&#xA;features demonstrated this post layout includes:&#xA;clean typography matching the pastebin/007 interfaces professional blue color scheme (#002a5c, #004085) rounded containers with subtle shadows monospace code blocks back-to-terminal navigation # example code block with ping service styling curl https://candace.cloud/ping # returns: &amp;#34;ive been visited X times&amp;#34; notice how this feels different from the terminal homepage but maintains the same underlying aesthetic philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>capturing the terminal aesthetic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/posts/terminal-aesthetic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/posts/terminal-aesthetic/</guid>
      <description>the candaceserver homepage has this amazing raw terminal feel that&amp;rsquo;s both nostalgic and modern.&#xA;design elements color palette dark background (#111) creates that terminal window feel bright green headings (#0f0) for that classic hacker vibe cyan links (#0ff) that shift to magenta when visited yellow on hover (#ff0) for that authentic terminal response typography monospace fonts throughout create consistency with actual terminal output.&#xA;tone the casual, lowercase writing style (&amp;ldquo;welcome to candaceserver&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;ive been visited X times&amp;rdquo;) feels personal and approachable while maintaining the technical aesthetic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&#xA;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.&#xA;Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
